Friends
Typescript one
Interview with Jade Jagger
Could you tell us a bit about yourself
Sure
First of all
Where were you born
I was born in London
Nationality because my mother's from Nicaragua
No
I'm living in Ibiza now
How long have you been there
I moved from London with my two daughters a cc and Amber
About 6 months ago
Are you happy there
Yeah very happy
We love y'all too alive
Ulta
My mother is a Spanish speaker and I feel more comfortable in the Latin country
Have you made any new friends
I made lots of new friends here
A few English
But my two best friends are Argentinian and Spanish what do you do for a living
Anna painter
Recently started a jewelry business with a friend
And that takes up most of my time
I want to do some modeling when I need the cash and what do you do in your free time
Well with a business and two young children I don't have much free time
I love reading and listening to music
What sort of music do you like
Put music and classical
Do you ever listen to The Rolling Stones
No never but don't tell my father
How often do you see your parents
Not very often
My mother's in you you look and my phone is off none too
But we will love big family get-together.
What's your favorite place in the world
That's a difficult question because I've been to so many amazing places
But I think Brazil is my favorite
The children of it that too
Finally
Can I ask you one last question
Who chose your name
I think my father chose it
My mother wanted me to have a Spanish name